A Guide to the Department of Confederate Military Records, 1859-1996
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Unit Records
  - Subseries 1: Artillery
    - Independent Batteries
      - Woolfork's Co. Va. Light Arty. (Ashland Artillery) (See Also Oversized - Box 1), 1862-1913 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Wright's Co. Va. Heavy Arty. (Halifax Artillery), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Richmond Howitzers Bn.
        - 1st Company (Anderson's Co. Va. Light Arty.) (See Also Oversized - Box 1) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 2), 1861-1913 (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - 2nd Company (Jones' Co. Va. Arty.) (See Also Oversized - Box 1) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 2), 1861-1908 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - 3rd Company (Smith's Co. Va. Arty.) (See Also Oversized - Box 1) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 2), 1861-1915 (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - 4th Company (Binford's Co. Vols.) (See Oversized - Drawer 2), 1861 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 1), 1892-1912 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Wise Legion - Co. A (Hart's Battery) (Kirby's Co.), n.d. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Cavalry
    - Regiments
      - 1st
        - Co. A (Newton Light Dragoons), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Hoge's Co.), 1904 (Box 14, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Rockbridge Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1900 (Box 14, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (2nd) (Washington Mounted Rifles), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Valley Rangers) (See Also Oversized - Box 2) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1862-1911 (Box 14, Box 5)
        - Co. F (Shepherdstown Troop), 1904 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Amelia Light Dragoons), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Loudoun Light Horse), 1916 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (Harrisonburg Cavalry), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 9)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Howard Dragoons), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1912-1916 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - 2nd
        - Co. A (Clay Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1911 (Box 14, Folder 12)
        - Co. B (Wise Troop), 1905 (Box 14, Folder 13)
        - Co. C (Botetourt Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1913 (Box 14, Folder 14)
        - Co. D (Franklin Rangers), 1910 (Box 14, Folder 15)
        - Co. E (Amherst Mounted Rangers), 1884-1904 (Box 14, Folder 16)
        - Co. F (Bedford Southside Dragoons), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 17)
        - Co. G (Radford Rangers), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 18)
        - Co. H (Appomattox Rangers), 1904-1906 (Box 14, Folder 19)
        - Co. I (Campbell Rangers) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 14, Folder 20)
        - Co. K (Albemarle Light Horse), 1884-1930 (Box 14, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - 3rd
        - Co. A (Boydton Cavalry), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 23)
        - Co. B (Old Dominion Dragoons), 1861-1913 (Box 14, Folder 24)
        - Co. C (Black Walnut Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1918 (Box 14, Folder 25)
        - Co. D (Charles City Light Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 14, Folder 26)
        - Co. E (Nottoway Troop), 1903-1905 (Box 14, Folder 27)
        - Co. F (New Kent Light Dragoons), 1905-1907 (Box 14, Folder 28)
        - Co. G (Cumberland Light Dragoons), 1908-1916 (Box 14, Folder 29)
        - Co. H (Catawba Troop), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 30)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Dinwiddie Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1906 (Box 14, Folder 31)
        - Co. K (Prince Edward Dragoons), 1898-1936 (Box 14, Folder 32)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1864 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - 4th
        - Co. A (Prince William Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1864 (Box 14, Folder 34)
        - Co. B (Chesterfield Light Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1864 (Box 14, Folder 35)
        - Co. C (Madison Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Box 2) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1863-1913 (Box 14, Folder 36)
        - Co. D (Little Fork Rangers) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1864-1913 (Box 14, Folder 37)
        - Co. E (Powhatan Troop) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1864-1919 (Box 14, Folder 38)
        - Co. F (Goochland Light Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1864-1896 (Box 14, Folder 39)
        - Co. G (Hanover Light Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1864-1912 (Box 14, Folder 40)
        - Co. H (Black Horse Troop) (See Also Oversized - Box 2) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1861-1907 (Box 14, Folder 41)
        - Co. I (Governor's Mounted Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 2) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1861-1913 (Box 14, Folder 42)
        - Co. K (McKinney's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1862-1910 (Box 14, Folder 43)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 44)
      - 5th (1861-1862)
        - Co. I (Chesapeake Cavalry), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - 5th (1862-1864)
        - Co. A (Gloucester Light Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Box 2) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1861 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        - Co. B (Windsor's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1908 (Box 15, Folder 3)
        - Co. C (Mebane's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1910 (Box 15, Folder 4)
        - Co. D (Petersburg Rangers), 1911 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        - Co. E (King & Queen Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 3), 1861 (Box 15, Folder 6)
        - Co. F (1st) (Shields Lancers), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 7)
        - Co. F (3rd) (Mathews Light Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 8)
        - Co. G (Randolph Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1909 (Box 15, Folder 9)
        - Co. H (James City Cavalry), 1896-1908 (Box 15, Folder 10)
        - Co. K (Pannill's Co.), 1911 (Box 15, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - 6th
        - Co. A (Loudoun Dragoons), 1909-1914 (Box 15, Folder 13)
        - Co. B (The Old Guard) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1861-1907 (Box 15, Folder 14)
        - Co. C (Rockingham Cavalry), 1909-1913 (Box 15, Folder 15)
        - Co. D (Clarke Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1906 (Box 15, Folder 16)
        - Co. E (2nd) (Pittsylvania Dragoons), 1914 (Box 15, Folder 17)
        - Co. F (Fairfax Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1861-1884 (Box 15, Folder 18)
        - Co. G (Halifax Cavalry), 1910-1913 (Box 15, Folder 19)
        - Co. H (Wise Dragoons), 1864-1914 (Box 15, Folder 20)
        - Co. I (Orange Rangers) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1907-1909 (Box 15, Folder 21)
        - Co. K (Loudoun Cavalry), 1909-1913 (Box 15, Folder 22)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1864-1919 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - 7th
        - Co. A (Mountain Rangers), 1913-1914 (Box 15, Folder 24)
        - Co. B (Letcher Brock's Gap Rifles), 1930 (Box 15, Folder 25)
        - Co. C (Shenandoah Rangers), 1908 (Box 15, Folder 26)
        - Co. D (Jordan's Co.), 1884-1910 (Box 15, Folder 27)
        - Co. E (Mountain Rangers) (See Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 15, Folder 28)
        - Co. F (Sheetz's Co.), 1904 (Box 15, Folder 29)
        - Co. G (Mason's Co.), 1927 (Box 15, Folder 30)
        - Co. H (Shoup's Co.), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 31)
        - Co. I (Shand's Co.), 1913 (Box 15, Folder 32)
        - Co. K (Miller's Co.), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 33)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1864-1912 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - 8th
        - Co. A (Smyth Dragoons), 1915 (Box 15, Folder 35)
        - Co. B (Nelson Rangers), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 36)
        - Co. C (Grayson Cavalry), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 37)
        - Co. D (Giles Troop), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 38)
        - Co. E (Border Rangers), 1898 (Box 15, Folder 39)
        - Co. F (Harman's Co.), 1910-1913 (Box 15, Folder 40)
        - Co. G (Mountain Rangers), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 41)
        - Co. H (Tazewell Troop), 1914-1915 (Box 15, Folder 42)
        - Co. I (Kanawha Rangers), 1862 (Box 15, Folder 43)
        - Co. K (Fairview Rifle Guards), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 44)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904-1914 (Box 15, Folder 45)
      - 9th
        - Co. A (Stafford Rangers), 1903-1908 (Box 15, Folder 46)
        - Co. B (Caroline Light Dragoons), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 47)
        - Co. C (Westmoreland Cavalry), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 48)
        - Co. D (Lancaster Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1906 (Box 15, Folder 49)
        - Co. E (Mercer Cavalry) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 50)
        - Co. F (Essex Light Dragoons), 1913 (Box 15, Folder 51)
        - Co. G (Lunenburg Light Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1861-1915 (Box 15, Folder 52)
        - Co. H (Virginia Rangers), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 53)
        - Co. I (Potomac Cavalry), 1904-1916 (Box 15, Folder 54)
        - Co. K (Richmond County Cavalry), 1911 (Box 15, Folder 55)
        - Miscellaneous, 1899-1907 (Box 15, Folder 56)
      - 10th
        - Co. A (Caskie's Mounted Rangers), 1912 (Box 15, Folder 57)
        - Co. B (Carolina Rangers), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 58)
        - Co. C (Flood's Co.), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 59)
        - Co. D (Wise Mounted Guard), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 60)
        - Co. E (2nd) (Hinton's Co.), 1906-1915 (Box 15, Folder 61)
        - Co. F (Albemarle Rangers), 1910-1912 (Box 15, Folder 62)
        - Co. G (Jackson Rangers) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 63)
        - Co. H (Valley Rangers), 1861 (Box 15, Folder 64)
        - Co. I (Henrico Light Dragoons), 1911 (Box 15, Folder 65)
        - Co. K (Texas Rangers), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 66)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 67)
      - 11th
        - Co. A (Myer's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Harness' Co.), 1863 (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Chipley's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (McDonald's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Hess' Co.), 1908 (Box 16, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Bath Cavalry), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Bath Guards), 1895-1913 (Box 16, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Pierce's Co.), 1884-1913 (Box 16, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (Ball's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1861 (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - Co. K (Weem's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1864-1904 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - 12th
        - Co. A (Glenn's Co.), 1905-1915 (Box 16, Folder 12)
        - Co. B (Baylor's Co.), 1904-1913 (Box 16, Folder 13)
        - Co. C (Ford's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 14)
        - Co. D (Kearney's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 15)
        - Co. F (Clark's Co.), 1904 (Box 16, Folder 16)
        - Co. G (Swindler's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 17)
        - Co. H (Randolph's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1913 (Box 16, Folder 18)
        - Co. I (Eastham's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1863-1904 (Box 16, Folder 19)
        - Co. K (Lutz's Co.), 1908 (Box 16, Folder 20)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1864 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - 13th
        - Co. A (Southampton Cavalry), 1907 (Box 16, Folder 22)
        - Co. B (Petersburg Cavalry), 1911 (Box 16, Folder 23)
        - Co. C (Riddick's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 24)
        - Co. D (Jackson's Avengers) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1861 (Box 16, Folder 25)
        - Co. E (Cockade Cavalry), 1893 (Box 16, Folder 26)
        - Co. F (Prince George Cavalry), 1913-1926 (Box 16, Folder 27)
        - Co. G (Surry Cavalry), 1906 (Box 16, Folder 28)
        - Co. H (Sussex Light Dragoons) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 16, Folder 29)
        - Co. I (Nansemond Cavalry), 1904 (Box 16, Folder 30)
        - Co. K (Burt's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 31)
        - Miscellaneous, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - 14th
        - Co. A (White's Company of Mounted Riflemen), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 33)
        - Co. B (Charlotte Cavalry), 1899-1921 (Box 16, Folder 34)
        - Co. C (Leckey's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 16, Folder 35)
        - Co. D (Jenkins Guards), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 36)
        - Co. E (Knott's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 37)
        - Co. F (2nd) (Smith's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 38)
        - Co. G (Valley Rangers), 1913 (Box 16, Folder 39)
        - Co. H (Rockbridge Dragoons, No. 2), 1913 (Box 16, Folder 40)
        - Co. I (Churchville Cavalry), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 41)
        - Co. K (Greenbrier Cavalry, No. 2) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1861-1914 (Box 16, Folder 42)
        - Miscellaneous, 1911 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      - 15th
        - Co. A (Sanford's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 44)
        - Co. B (Gantt's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 45)
        - Co. C (Capp's Co.), 1912 (Box 16, Folder 46)
        - Co. D (Harding Jr.'s Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 47)
        - Co. E (Arnold's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 48)
        - Co. F (Cooper's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 49)
        - Co. G (Cooke's Co.), 1911-1913 (Box 16, Folder 50)
        - Co. H (Brawner's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 51)
        - Co. I (Bonney's Co.), 1911 (Box 16, Folder 52)
        - Co. K (Scott's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 53)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 54)
      - 16th
        - Co. A (Stevenson's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 16, Folder 55)
        - Co. B (Gent's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 56)
        - Co. C (Hankins' Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 57)
        - Co. D (Morris' Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 58)
        - Co. F (Taylor's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 59)
        - Co. G (Parks' Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 60)
        - Co. H (Kendrick's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 61)
        - Co. I (Peery's Co.), 1905-1911 (Box 16, Folder 62)
        - Co. K (Anderson's Co.), 1913 (Box 16, Folder 63)
        - Miscellaneous, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 64)
      - 17th
        - Co. A (French's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 65)
        - Co. B (Armesy's Co.), 1913 (Box 16, Folder 66)
        - Co. C (Tavenner's Co.) (See Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 16, Folder 67)
        - Co. E (Straley's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 68)
        - Co. F (Night Hawk Rangers), 1915 (Box 16, Folder 69)
        - Co. H (Parson's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 70)
        - Co. K (Pifer's Co.), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 71)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 72)
      - 18th
        - Co. A (Taylor's Co.), 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Stump's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Ginevan's Co.), 1911 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Makely's Co.), 1917 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (2nd) (McNeill's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1863-1918 (Box 17, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Muse's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (2nd) (Ervin's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1861-1907 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Imboden's Co.), 1907-1915 (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (Warden's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - 19th
        - Co. A (Down's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1862-1863 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        - Co. C (Kessler's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - Co. F (McNeill's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 13)
        - Co. I (Marshall's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 14)
        - Co. K (Norris' Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1863 (Box 17, Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - 20th
        - Co. A (Evans' Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1863-1906 (Box 17, Folder 17)
        - Co. B (Arnett's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 18)
        - Co. C (Hutton's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 19)
        - Co. D (Corder's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 20)
        - Co. G (Neal's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - 21st
        - Co. A (Halsey's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1863 (Box 17, Folder 22)
        - Co. B (Edmundson's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 23)
        - Co. C (2nd) (Branscom's Co.), 1905 (Box 17, Folder 24)
        - Co. D (2nd) (Logan's Co.), 1912-1913 (Box 17, Folder 25)
        - Co. E (1st) (Count's Co.), 1911-1921 (Box 17, Folder 26)
        - Co. F (Gray's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 27)
        - Co. G (2nd) (Dobyn's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1900 (Box 17, Folder 28)
        - Co. H (Summer's Co.), 1913 (Box 17, Folder 29)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Pasley's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 30)
        - Co. K (Oliver's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 31)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - 22nd
        - Co. A (Fuller's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 33)
        - Co. B (Riffe's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 34)
        - Co. C (Stanfield's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 35)
        - Co. D (Ball's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1861 (Box 17, Folder 36)
        - Co. E (Baldwin's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 37)
        - Co. F (Brown's Co.), 1914 (Box 17, Folder 38)
        - Co. G (Moore's Co.), 1910 (Box 17, Folder 39)
        - Co. H (Higginbotham's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 40)
        - Co. I (Sample's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 41)
        - Co. K (Francis' Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 42)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - 23rd
        - Co. A (Triplett's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 44)
        - Co. B. (Patterson's Co.), 1912 (Box 17, Folder 45)
        - Co. C (White's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 4), 1864 (Box 17, Folder 46)
        - Co. E (Lovett's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 47)
        - Co. F (Drew's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 48)
        - Co. G (Riddlegerger's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 49)
        - Co. H (Pollock's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 50)
        - Co. I (Moore's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 51)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Adams' Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 52)
        - Co. M (Davis' Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 53)
      - 24th
        - Co. A (Green's Co.), 1913 (Box 17, Folder 54)
        - Co. B (McGruder's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1911 (Box 17, Folder 55)
        - Co. C (Littleton's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1907-1916 (Box 17, Folder 56)
        - Co. D (Clopton's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1903 (Box 17, Folder 57)
        - Co. E (Blake's Co.), 1916 (Box 17, Folder 58)
        - Co. F (Allen's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 59)
        - Co. G (Rodger's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 60)
        - Co. H (Hamlet's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 61)
        - Co. I (Barham's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 62)
        - Co. K (Smith's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884 (Box 17, Folder 63)
        - Miscellaneous, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 64)
      - 25th
        - Co. A (McConnell's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 65)
        - Co. B (Larner's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 66)
        - Co. C (Collings' Co.), 1912 (Box 17, Folder 67)
        - Co. D (Smith's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 68)
        - Co. E (Radford's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 69)
        - Co. F (Thomas' Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 70)
        - Co. G (Gibson's Co.), 1913 (Box 17, Folder 71)
        - Co. H (Larner's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 72)
        - Co. I (Lee Rangers) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1884-1905 (Box 17, Folder 73)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 74)
      - 26th
        - Co. A (Jarvis' Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 75)
        - Co. B (Davisson's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 76)
        - Co. E (McGuffin's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 77)
        - Co. F (Lee's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 78)
        - Co. I (Cloud's Co.), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 79)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Battalions
      - 27th
        - Co. A (McConnell's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Larner's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Collings' Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Smith's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Radford's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1904 (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Thomas' Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Gibson's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Larner's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (Lee Rangers), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - 34th
        - Co. A (Witcher's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 11)
        - Co. B (Straton's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - Co. C (McDowell Partisan Rangers), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - Co. D (Carter's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 14)
        - Co. E (Yost's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 15)
        - Co. G (Webb's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 16)
        - Co. H (Boyd's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 17)
        - Miscellaneous, 1908 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - 35th
        - Co. A (White's Rebels) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1909 (Box 18, Folder 19)
        - Co. B (Chiswell's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 20)
        - Co. C (Grubb's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 21)
        - Co. D (Trayhern's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 22)
        - Co. E (Grabill's Co.), 1915 (Box 18, Folder 23)
        - Co. F (Ferneyhough's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 24)
        - Co. H, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 25)
        - Miscellaneous, 1864-1894 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - 36th
        - Co. A (Smith's Co.), 1907 (Box 18, Folder 27)
        - Co. C (Kirtley's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 28)
        - Co. D (Zane's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 29)
        - Co. G, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 30)
        - Miscellaneous, 1906-1907 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - 37th
        - Co. A (Claiborne's Co.), 1910-1916 (Box 18, Folder 32)
        - Co. B (Earle's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 33)
        - Co. C (Tapscott's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 34)
        - Co. D (Brown's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 35)
        - Co. E (Phelps' Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 36)
        - Co. F (Norman's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 37)
        - Co. G (Bridges' Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 38)
        - Co. H (Payne's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 39)
        - Co. I (Young's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 40)
        - Co. K (Pack's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 41)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - 39th
        - Co. A (Pifer's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 43)
        - Co. B (Randolph's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 44)
        - Co. C (Lee's Body Guard), 1894 (Box 18, Folder 45)
        - Co. D (Page's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 46)
        - Capt. John W. Opie's Co., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 47)
        - Miscellaneous, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 48)
      - 43rd
        - Co. A (Foster's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 49)
        - Co. B (Smith's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 50)
        - Co. C (Chapman's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 51)
        - Co. D (Montjoy's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 52)
        - Co. E (Chapman's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 2), 1900 (Box 18, Folder 53)
        - Co. F (Frankland's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 54)
        - Co. G (Richards' Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 55)
        - Co. H (Baylor's Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 56)
        - Artillery Co., 1911 (Box 18, Folder 57)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904-1916 (Box 18, Folder 58)
      - 46th
        - Co. A (Jarvis' Co.), 1905 (Box 18, Folder 59)
      - 47th
        - Co. B (Newberry's Co.), 1910 (Box 18, Folder 60)
        - Co. E, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Independent Companies
      - Capt. Peyton Coles' Co. Va. Cav. (Green Mountain Rangers), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 62)
      - Capt. John J. Young's Co. Va. Cav. (Harbor Guard), 1914 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Subseries 3: Infantry
    - Regiments
      - 1st
        - Field & Staff Officers (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1879-1884 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - Co. A (Richmond Greys) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1879-1884 (Box 19, Folder 2)
        - Co. B (Richmond City Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1860-1918 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Co. C (Montgomery Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1879-1918 (Box 19, Folder 4)
        - Co. D (Old Dominion Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1879-1918 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        - Co. E (Washington Volunteers) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1861-1918 (Box 19, Folder 6)
        - Co. F (Beauregard Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1879-1918 (Box 19, Folder 7)